const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '900 − 201 =', answer: '699', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '800 − 602 =', answer: '198', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '700 − 403 =', answer: '297', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '600 − 104 =', answer: '496', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '500 − 205 =', answer: '295', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '600 − 201 =', answer: '399', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '500 − 304 =', answer: '196', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '700 − 309 =', answer: '391', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '800 − 306 =', answer: '494', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '700 − 203 =', answer: '497', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];